<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!--<!DOCTYPE article PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD Simplied DocBook XML V1.1//EN" "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/simple/1.1/sdocbook.dtd"-->
<!--<!DOCTYPE article PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.3//EN" "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.3/docbookx.dtd"-->
<!DOCTYPE article PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.3//EN" "../Common/docbook/xml/4.3/docbookx.dtd"
[
<!ENTITY addkey1 SYSTEM "addkey1.cdata">
<!ENTITY addkey2 SYSTEM "addkey2.cdata">
<!ENTITY downloads SYSTEM "../Common/download.xml">
<!ENTITY name "VSAddin">
]>
<article id="V1EclipsePlugIn.user">
    <title>VersionOne Eclipse Pl;ugin User Guide</title>
    <section id="description">
        <title>Description</title>
        <para>
            The VersionOne Eclipse Plugin (V1EclipsePlugIn) provides direct interaction with VersionOne developer tasks from within Eclipse.  
            This enables Java developers to update VersionOne task status, estimates, remaining effort, etc., without 
            needing to leave the comfortable confines of the Eclipse Environment.
        </para>
    </section>
    <section id="systemreqs">
        <title>System Requirements</title>
        <para>
            VersionOne: 7.3 or above
        </para>
        <para>
            Client Workstation:
            <itemizedlist>
                <listitem><para>IDE&mdash;Eclipse 3.3.1.1 (Europa) </para></listitem>
            </itemizedlist>
        </para>
    </section>
    &downloads;
    <section id="installation">
        <title>1. Installation</title>        
        <section id="install.setup">
            <para>Use the following steps to install the VersionOne Eclipse Plugin
                <orderedlist>
                    <listitem>Remove any existing VersionOne integration</listitem>
                    <listitem>Unzip ***** into a temporary location</listitem>
                    <listitem>Copy the features and plugins directory into ECLIPSE_HOME</listitem>
                </orderedlist>            
            </para>
        </section>
        <section id="install.configure">
            <title>2.  Configure</title>
            <para>
                Select <emphasis>Preferences...</emphasis> from the <emphasis>Window</emphasis> 
                menu, and navigate to the VersionOne settings as show in <xref
                    linkend="install.configure.options"/>.
                <figure
                    id="install.configure.options">
                    <title>Configuration Options Screen</title>
                    <graphic fileref="Options.JPG"/>
                </figure>
                
                Enter the configuration parameters as specified in the table below and click <emphasis>Validate Connection</emphasis> to ensure that
                the add-in can both access VersionOne’s API and authenticate using the supplied username and password.				
                If the add-in is not configured correctly, or if VersionOne is unavailable (e.g. you are off-network), both the Projects and Tasks windows will inform you 
                of the appropriate error, and provide an option to modify the add-in configuration.
                
                <table
                    frame="none" id="install.configure.table">
                    <title>VSAddin Configuration Parameters</title>
                    <tgroup cols="2">
                        <thead>
                            <row>
                                <entry>Parameter</entry>
                                <entry>Description</entry>
                            </row>
                        </thead>
                        <tbody>
                            <row>
                                <entry>Enable</entry>
                                <entry>Allows you to enable/disable the Plugin</entry>
                            </row>
                            <row>
                                <entry>Windows Integrated Authentication</entry>
                                <entry>Enables Windows Integraten Authentication</entry>
                            </row>
                            <row>
                                <entry>Application URL</entry>
                                <entry>VersionOne installation URL</entry>
                            </row>
                            <row>
                                <entry>Username</entry>
                                <entry>User that will access VersionOne.</entry>
                            </row>
                            <row>
                                <entry>Password</entry>
                                <entry>Password for the username above.  If the authenticationType is WindowsIntegrated this should be left blank if the username is blank (to use the currently logged on user account).</entry>
                            </row>
                            <row>
                                <entry>Effort Tracking</entry>
                                <entry>Flag for Effort Tracking.  If VersionOne has effort tracking enabled, check this box to add the
                                    <emphasis>Effort</emphasis> and <emphasis>Done</emphasis> columns</entry>
                            </row>
                        </tbody>
                    </tgroup>
                </table>
            </para>
        </section>
    </section>
    <section id="usage">
        <title>Usage</title>
        <para>
            ***** Work here and below
            The add-in consists of two dockable windows, <emphasis>VersionOne Projects</emphasis> and <emphasis>VersionOne Tasks</emphasis>, 
            accessible via the View menu’s Other Windows sub-menu.  
            Additionally, the built-in Visual Studio properties grid is populated with relevant properties dependent on the user’s context and focus within either window.
        </para>
        <section id="usage.project">
            <title>Selecting Projects</title>
            
            <para>As shown in <xref linkend="usage.project.figure"
            />, the VersionOne Projects dockable window displays a project tree populated with your current projects. 
                To access this window, go to the View menu, select the Other Windows sub-menu, and select VersionOne Projects. 
                To choose a specific project to work on, simply navigate the tree and select it.
            </para>
            <para>
                Note that your project selection is maintained between uses of Visual Studio (per user, via Documents And Settings), 
                so after you select the project you may close this window to preserve real estate within the IDE.  The Task Window
                (discussed next) displays the current project name in its’ window title for project context.	
            </para>
            <figure id="usage.project.figure">
                <title>Projects Window</title>
                <graphic fileref="Projects.JPG"/>
            </figure>
        </section>
        <section id="usage.tasks">
            <title>Updating Tasks</title>
            <para>
                Like the VersionOne Projects window, the Tasks window is accessible by selecting VersionOne Tasks via the View menu’s Other Windows sub-menu.
                Once you’ve selected a project you’re working on, the Tasks window will display a grid listing all tasks that belong to you.
                To update a task, either modify the attribute directly in the tasks grid (for the most common properties) or, after selecting the row,
                use the Visual Studio properties grid to edit the extended set of task properties.  Once you’re finished updating a Task, click the Save button to update the task in VersionOne.				
            </para>
            <figure id="usage.tasks.figure">
                <title>Tasks Window</title>
                <graphic fileref="Tasks.JPG"/>
            </figure>
        </section>
    </section>
    <section id="section.footer">
        <title/>
        <para>Copyright &copy; <?dbtimestamp format="Y"?>, VersionOne, Inc. All rights reserved. This document was generated <?dbtimestamp format="Y-m-d H:M:S"?>.</para>
    </section>
</article>
